A Guide to the The Photographic Archive of Fairfax County, Virginia - The Slide Collection, 1961-1998
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Ravensworth, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-73
- Ravensworth, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-74
- Ravensworth, Computer, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-75
- Ravensworth, Computer, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-76
- Ravensworth, Lib Ops, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-77
- Ravensworth, Acquisitions, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-78
- Ravensworth, Microfiche, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-79
- Ravensworth, Microfiche, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-80
- Ravensworth, Planning, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-81
- Ravensworth, Planning, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-82
- Ravensworth, Planning, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-83
- Ravensworth, Planning, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-84
- Ravensworth, Planning, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-85
- Ravensworth, Planning, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-86
- Ravensworth, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-87
- Ravensworth, Cataloging tapes, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-88
- Ravensworth, Cataloging Mary Poppins VHS tape, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-89
- Ravensworth, Cataloging, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-90
- Ravensworth, Cataloging, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-91
- Ravensworth, Cataloging, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-92
- Ravensworth, Cataloging, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-93
- Ravensworth, Cataloging, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-94
- Ravensworth, Cataloging, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-95
- Ravensworth, Cataloging, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-96
- Ravensworth, Cataloging, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-97
- Ravensworth, Cataloging, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-98
- Ravensworth, Cataloging, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-99
- Ravensworth, Talking Books, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-100
- Ravensworth, Talking Books, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-101
- Ravensworth, Talking Books, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-102
- Ravensworth, Talking Books, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-103
- Ravensworth, Talking Books, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-104
- Ravensworth, Talking Books, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-105
- Ravensworth, Talking Books, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RAV-106
- Heron House, Friends of the Reston Library Program, 1967; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-1
- Hunters Woods Library, Reston, 1972; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-2
- Hunters Woods Library, Reston, 1972; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-3
- Hunters Woods Library, Reston, 1972; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-4
- Hunters Woods Library, Reston, 1972; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-5
- Hunters Woods Library, Reston, 1972; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-6
- Hunters Woods Library, Reston, 1972; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-7
- Hunters Woods Library, Reston, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-8
- Hunters Woods Library, Reston, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-9
- Hunters Woods Library, Reston, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-10
- Hunters Woods Library, Reston, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-11
- Hunters Woods Library, Reston, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-12
- Hunters Woods Library, Reston, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-13
- Hunters Woods Library, Reston, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-14
- Hunters Woods Library, Reston, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-15
- Reston Library, Hats program, 1985; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-16
- Reston Library, Hats program, 1985; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-17
- Reston Library, Hats program, 1985; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-18
- Reston Library, Hats program, 1985; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-19
- Bowman House, Reston Friends of the Library Meeting, 1966; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-20
- Hunters Woods Library, Reston, 1972; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-21
- Reston Library, Book discussion, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-22
- Hunters Woods Library, Reston, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-23
- Hunters Woods Library, Reston, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-24
- Hunters Woods Library, Reston, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-25
- Hunters Woods Library, Reston, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RR-26
- Richard Byrd Library, Exterior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-1
- Richard Byrd Library, Circulation Desk, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-2
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-3
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-4
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-5
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-6
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-7
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-8
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-9
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-10
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-11
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-12
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-13
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-14
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-15
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-16
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-17
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-18
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-19
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-20
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-21
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-22
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-23
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-24
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-25
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-26
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-27
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-28
- Richard Byrd Library, Childrens program, 1973 June; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-29
- Richard Byrd Library, Display, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-30
- Richard Byrd Library, Display, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-31
- Richard Byrd Library, Display, 1973; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-32
- Richard Byrd Library, Stitches Happening, 1973 July 12; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-33
- Richard Byrd Library, Stitches Happening, 1973 July 12; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-34
- Richard Byrd Library, Stitches Happening, 1973 July 12; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-35
- Richard Byrd Library, Stitches Happening, 1973 July 12; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-36
- Richard Byrd Library, Stitches Happening, 1973 July 12; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-37
- Richard Byrd Library, Stitches Happening, 1973 July 12; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-38
- Richard Byrd Library, Stitches Happening, 1973 July 12; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-39
- Richard Byrd Library, Exterior, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-40
- Richard Byrd Library, Exterior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-41
- Richard Byrd Library, Exterior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-42
- Richard Byrd Library, Exterior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-43
- Richard Byrd Library, Circulation Desk, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-44
- Richard Byrd Library, "Fairfax County Information" brochures, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-45
- Richard Byrd Library, Stacks, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-46
- Richard Byrd Library, Display, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-47
- Richard Byrd Library, Exterior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-RB-48
- Sherwood Library, Interior construction, 1971; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-1
- Sherwood Library, Interior construction, 1971; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-2
- Sherwood Library, Interior construction, 1971; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-3
- Sherwood Library, Bookmobile at Spring Garden Apartments, 1973 June; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-4
- Sherwood Library, Bookmobile, 1973 June; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-5
- Sherwood Library, Bookmobile, 1973 June; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-6
- Sherwood Library, Bookmobile, 1973 June; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-7
- Sherwood Library, Bookmobile, 1973 June; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-8
- Sherwood Library, Bookmobile, 1973 June; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-9
- Sherwood Library, Bookmobile, 1973 June; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-10
- Sherwood Library, Bookmobile, 1973 June; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-11
- Sherwood Library, Bookmobile, 1973 June; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-12
- Sherwood Library, Bookmobile, 1973 June; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-13
- Sherwood Library, Exterior, 1983; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-14
- Sherwood Library, Exterior, 1983; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-15
- Sherwood Library, Exterior, 1983; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-16
- Sherwood Library, Exterior, 1983; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-17
- Sherwood Library, Sign, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-18
- Sherwood Library, Children's Section, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-19
- Sherwood Library, Circulation Desk, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-20
- Sherwood Library, Magazine Rack, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-21
- Sherwood Library, Microfilm, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-22
- Sherwood Library, Upstairs, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-23
- Sherwood Library, Reference, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-24
- Sherwood Library, Circulation Desk-Information, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-25
- Sherwood Library, Interior, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-26
- Sherwood Library, Interior, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-27
- Sherwood Library, Interior, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-28
- Sherwood Library, Interior, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-29
- Sherwood Library, Interior, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-30
- Sherwood Library, Interior, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-31
- Sherwood Library, Interior, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-32
- Sherwood Library, Concert, 1985; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-33
- Sherwood Library, Interior, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-34
- Sherwood Library, Concert, 1985; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-35
- Sherwood Library, Valentines, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-36
- Sherwood Library, Exterior, c. 1983; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-37
- Sherwood Library, Exterior, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-38
- Sherwood Library, Bookmobile, 1973 June; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-39
- Sherwood Library, Bookmobile, 1973 June; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-SH-40
- Thomas Jefferson Library, Exterior, 1971; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-TJ-1
- Thomas Jefferson Library, Masks program, 1985; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-TJ-2
- Thomas Jefferson Library, Masks program, 1985; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-TJ-3
- Thomas Jefferson Library, Masks program, 1985; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-TJ-4
- Thomas Jefferson Library, Masks program, 1985; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-TJ-5
- Thomas Jefferson Library, Puppets program, 1985; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-TJ-6
- Thomas Jefferson Library, Puppets program, 1985; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-TJ-7
- Thomas Jefferson Library, Puppets program, 1985; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-TJ-8
- Thomas Jefferson Library, Exterior, 1971; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-TJ-9
- Thomas Jefferson Library, Patron, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-TJ-10
- Tysons-Pimmit Library, Exterior, 1983; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-TY-1
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Interior, Meeting Room, 1967; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-1
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Interior, Setting Up Shelves, 1967; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-2
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Interior, 1967; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-3
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Interior, 1967; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-4
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Interior, 1967; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-5
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Interior, 1967; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-6
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Exterior, 1971; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-7
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Exterior, 1971; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-8
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Exterior, 1971; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-9
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Interior, Staff Luncheon, 1971; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-10
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-11
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-12
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-13
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-14
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-15
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-16
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-17
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile/Story Hour, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-18
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Interior, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-19
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-20
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-21
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-22
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-23
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-24
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-25
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-26
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-27
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-28
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-29
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Interior, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-30
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Interior, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-31
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Interior, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-32
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-33
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-34
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-35
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-36
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Interior, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-37
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Interior, Circulation Desk, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-38
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Interior, Library Card Registration, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-39
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-40
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-41
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-42
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-43
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-44
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-45
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-46
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-47
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-48
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-49
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-50
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-51
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-52
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Sign, 1983; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-53
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Seniors, 1985; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-54
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Seniors, 1985; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-55
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Seniors, 1985; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-56
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Seniors-Bible, 1985; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-57
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Exterior, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-58
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-59
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Bookmobile Visit, 1973; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-60
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Interior, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-61
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Interior, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-62
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Interior, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-63
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Interior, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-64
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Exterior, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-65
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Exterior, 1983; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-66
- Woodrow Wilson Library, Patron using photocopier, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-LIB-WW-67
- Oath Taken By Justices, Fairfax County Court, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-OATH-1
- Annandale Elementary School (photo by Nan Netherton), 1976; Box 4: FXCO-SCHOOLS-ANNA-ES-1
- Annandale High School, aerial (photo by Charles Baptie), Undated; Box 4: FXCO-SCHOOLS-ANNA-H-1
- Annandale High School, aerial (photo by Charles Baptie), Undated; Box 4: FXCO-SCHOOLS-ANNA-H-2
- Hayfield Secondary School, Library, 1969; Box 4: FXCO-SCHOOLS-HAYF-1
- Hayfield Secondary School, Library, 1969; Box 4: FXCO-SCHOOLS-HAYF-2
- Hayfield Secondary School, Library, 1969; Box 4: FXCO-SCHOOLS-HAYF-3
- Hayfield Secondary School, Library, 1969; Box 4: FXCO-SCHOOLS-HAYF-4
- Legato School, Relocated, 1974; Box 4: FXCO-SCHOOLS-LEGA-1
- Legato School, Relocated, 1974; Box 4: FXCO-SCHOOLS-LEGA-3
- Legato School, Relocated, 1974; Box 4: FXCO-SCHOOLS-LEGA-4
- Legato School, Relocated, 1974; Box 4: FXCO-SCHOOLS-LEGA-5
- Terraset Elementary School (Photo by Susanne Anderson), 1977 October; Box 4: FXCO-SCHOOLS-TERR-1
- Terraset Elementary School (Photo by Susanne Anderson), 1977 October; Box 4: FXCO-SCHOOLS-TERR-2
- Terraset Elementary School (Photo by Susanne Anderson), 1977 October; Box 4: FXCO-SCHOOLS-TERR-3
- Terraset Elementary School (Photo by Susanne Anderson), 1977 October; Box 4: FXCO-SCHOOLS-TERR-4
- Terraset Elementary School (Photo by Susanne Anderson), 1977 October; Box 4: FXCO-SCHOOLS-TERR-5
- Fairfax County Seal, Undated; Box 4: FXCO-SE-1
- Arms of Thomas, Sixth Lord Fairfax, 1980; Box 4: FXFA-1
- Tomb of Thomas, Sixth Lord Fairfax, Winchester, VA, 1973; Box 4: FXFA-2
- Tomb of Thomas, Sixth Lord Fairfax, New Tomb and Memorial Plaque, Winchester, VA (Photo by Don Sweig), 1973; Box 4: FXFA-3
- Thomas, Sixth Lord Fairfax, Coffin Plate, 1973; Box 4: FXFA-4
- Greenway Court, Lord Fairfax's Will, Winchester, VA. Clerk's Office Showing Signatures and Seal, 1973 August; Box 4: FXFA-5
- Greenway Court, Lord Fairfax's Will, Winchester, VA. Clerk's Office Showing Signatures and Seal, 1973 August; Box 4: FXFA-6
- Thomas, Sixth Lord Fairfax, Memorial Plaque (photo by Don Sweig), 1975; Box 4: FXFA-7
- Thomas, Sixth Lord Fairfax, Memorial Plaque (photo by Don Sweig), 1975; Box 4: FXFA-8
- Greenway Court, Arsenal or Powder House, Original Building Still Stands (photo by Roger R. Dawson), 1968 February; Box 4: FXFA-9
- Greenway Court, Old Flags Draped Over George Washington and Lord Fairfax, Old Desk Office (photo Roger R. Dawson), Undated; Box 4: FXFA-10
- Greenway Court, at the Office Doorway, Lord Fairfax and George Washington (photo Roger R. Dawson), 1968; Box 4: FXFA-11
- Tomb of 1st Lord Fairfax and Wife, Otley Church, Undated; Box 4: FXFA-12
- Towlston Grange(?), old house on schoolgrounds, Undated; Box 4: FXFA-13
- Nun Appleton, Gen. Fairfax's House, Undated; Box 4: FXFA-14
- Nun Appleton, Gen. Fairfax's House, Undated; Box 4: FXFA-15
- Nun Appleton, Gen. Fairfax's House, Undated; Box 4: FXFA-16
- Old Stone Office Bldg Where Lord Fairfax Madde Land Deals Fast Involving Northern Neck of Virginia, Many Famous Transfers Made (photo Roger R. Dawson), 1968; Box 4: FXFA-17
- Fairfax Tomb (?) with Coats of Arms, Undated; Box 4: FXFA-18
- Monument to Sir Humphrey Lee d. 1632, Church at Acton Burnell, Undated; Box 4: FXFA-19
- Bolton Percy Church, Undated; Box 4: FXFA-20
- Bolton Percy Church, Fairfax Tomb, Undated; Box 4: FXFA-21
- Bolton Percy Church, Fairfax Tomb, Undated; Box 4: FXFA-22
- Lee Hall, Residence of Lee Ancestors, Undated; Box 4: FXFA-23
- Sulgrave, Home of the Washington's ancestors, Undated; Box 4: FXFA-24
- Towlston Grange, Yorkshire, Undated; Box 4: FXFA-25
- Sally Fairfax Home, Undated; Box 4: FXFA-26
- Leeds Castle, 1969; Box 4: FXFA-27
- Fairfax Coat of Arms, Otley Church, Undated; Box 4: FXFA-28
- Louisa Fairfax Catlett, 1969; Box 4: FXFA-29
- Mary Randolph Fairfax, Undated; Box 4: FXFA-30
- Bryan Fairfax's drawing, 1969; Box 4: FXFA-31
- George Mason University, President's House, Undated; Box 4: GMU-1
- George Mason Univerisity, Campus, 1974; Box 4: GMU-3
- George Mason Univerisity, Parking Lot, 1974; Box 4: GMU-4
- George Mason College, Map Rendering, 1970; Box 4: GMU-5
- Patowmack Canal Company Seal, 1980; Box 4: GREA-1
- Hagley Museum, Wilmington, Dela+C2168ware, Diorama of Building the Potamac Canal, 1977; Box 4: GREA-2
- Great Falls, Patowmack Canal, 1968; Box 4: GREA-3
- Great Falls, Patowmack Canal, 1968; Box 4: GREA-4
- Great Falls, Patowmack Canal, Matildaville, 1968; Box 4: GREA-5
- Great Falls, Patowmack Canal, 1968; Box 4: GREA-6
- Great Falls, Patowmack Canal, 1968; Box 4: GREA-7
- Great Falls, Patowmack Canal, Matildaville, 1968; Box 4: GREA-8
- Great Falls, Patowmack Canal, Matildaville, 1968; Box 4: GREA-9
- Great Falls, Patowmack Canal, Matildaville, 1968; Box 4: GREA-10
- Great Falls, Patowmack Canal, 1968; Box 4: GREA-11
- Great Falls, Patowmack Canal, 1968; Box 4: GREA-12
- Great Falls, Patowmack Canal, 1968; Box 4: GREA-13
- Great Falls, Patowmack Canal, 1968; Box 4: GREA-14
- Great Falls, Patowmack Canal, 1968; Box 4: GREA-15
- Great Falls, Patowmack Canal, 1968; Box 4: GREA-16
- Great Falls, Patowmack Canal, 1968; Box 4: GREA-17
- Great Falls, Patowmack Canal, 1968; Box 4: GREA-18
- Great Falls, Patowmack Canal, 1968; Box 4: GREA-19
- Great Falls, Patowmack Canal, 1968; Box 4: GREA-20
- Great Falls, Patowmack Canal, 1968; Box 4: GREA-21
- Great Falls, Patowmack Canal, 1968; Box 4: GREA-22
- Great Falls, 1968; Box 4: GREA-23
- Great Falls, 1968; Box 4: GREA-24
- Great Falls from Maryland (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 4: GREA-25
- Great Falls in Flood (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 4: GREA-26
- Great Falls Sunset (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 4: GREA-27
- Great Falls Bridge (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 4: GREA-28
- Great Falls (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 4: GREA-29
- Great Falls, 1970; Box 4: GREA-30
- Great Falls, 1970; Box 4: GREA-31
- Great Falls, Undated; Box 4: GREA-32
- Great Falls, Undated; Box 4: GREA-33
- Great Falls, Undated; Box 4: GREA-34
- Great Falls, Undated; Box 4: GREA-35
- Great Falls, Undated; Box 4: GREA-36
- Great Falls, Undated; Box 4: GREA-37
- Great Falls, Undated; Box 4: GREA-38
- Great Falls Sunset (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 4: GREA-39
- Great Falls from Maryland (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 4: GREA-40
- Great Falls Bridge (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 4: GREA-41
- Great Falls (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 4: GREA-42
- Great Falls, Patowmack Canal, Matildaville, 1968; Box 4: GREA-43
- Green Spring Farm, House, 1976; Box 4: GREE-2
- Green Spring Farm, Exterior, Fairfax County Council of the Arts Headquarters, 1976; Box 4: GREE-3
- Green Spring Farm, Garden View, Fairfax County Council of the Arts Headquarters (photo by Nan Netherton), 1976; Box 4: GREE-4
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-2
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-4
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-5
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-7
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-8
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-9
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-10
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-11
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-12
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-13
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-14
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-15
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-16
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-17
- Gunston Hall, Tomb of George Mason, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-18
- Gunston Hall, Tomb of George Mason and Anne Mason, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-19
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-20
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-21
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-22
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-23
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-24
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-25
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-26
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-27
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-28
- Gunston Hall, Undated; Box 4: GUNS-29
- Gunston Hall, Undated; Box 4: GUNS-30
- Gunston Hall, Undated; Box 4: GUNS-31
- Gunston Hall, Undated; Box 4: GUNS-32
- Gunston Hall, Undated; Box 4: GUNS-33
- Gunston Hall, Undated; Box 4: GUNS-34
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-35
- Gunston Hall, Undated; Box 4: GUNS-36
- Gunston Hall, Undated; Box 4: GUNS-37
- Gunston Hall, Undated; Box 4: GUNS-38
- Gunston Hall, Undated; Box 4: GUNS-39
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-40
- Gunston Hall, 1968; Box 4: GUNS-41
- Havener House, Centerville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 4: HAVE-1 (1 of 3)
- Havener House, Centerville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 4: HAVE-1 (2 of 3)
- Havener House, Centerville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 4: HAVE-1 (3 of 3)
- Havener House, Centerville, 1966; Box 4: HAVE-2 (1 of 3)
- Havener House, Centerville, 1966; Box 4: HAVE-2 (2 of 3)
- Havener House, Centerville, 1966; Box 4: HAVE-2 (3 of 3)
- Havener House, Centerville, 1966 August; Box 4: HAVE-3 (1 of 5)